Fabio Rodriguez

Full Stack Software Engineer

I am a Full Stack Web Developer experienced in React, Nextis, TypeScript and Tailwind. I love creating products from the ground up, and the continuous learning necessary in the tech world. I currently work as a Technical Support Engineer where I'm constantly solving logical problems and finding solutions for our customers.













Education

Front End Masters

2023

Continuous Online Web Development education ranging from Computer Science to Front and Back End Development alike.

Makers Academy

2021

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp based in London.

- Built several applications using TDD, MVP
- Pair programmed for over 300 hours.
- Agile/XP

University of Venezuela - UCV 2018

Bachelor Degree in Modern Languages with Translations and Interpreting

Skills

Coding Languages

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Python, Java, Ruby, SQL

Frameworks

React, NextJs, Django, Springboot, Rails

DBs & Other Technologies

Firestore/Firebase, PostgreSQL, Neo4j, Redis, MongoDB, Tailwind, Figma, AWS

Certifications

Systems Thinking -MIT

Experience

Technical Support Engineer -2021 - Current ServiceNow

- Provide technical support and assistance to customers, troubleshooting and resolving issues related to the ServiceNow
- · Administer and configure ServiceNow instances, including user access, roles, and permissions.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to identify, diagnose, and resolve complex technical problems.
- Develop and maintain documentation, including knowledge base articles and standard operating procedures.
- Manage and prioritise incidents, problems, and changes according to established service level agreements (SLAs).

Freelance Software Developer 2021 - Current

- Worked with a diverse range of clients, including small businesses and individuals, to develop and deploy custom web solutions.
- Developed responsive and user-friendly websites using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and React/Nextjs ensuring cross-browser compatibility and mobile responsiveness.
- · Collaborated closely with clients to gather project requirements, identify objectives, and deliver projects on time and within budget.

Team Manager - Sitel UK

2017 - 2021

- Trained, coached, and supervised new staff members.
- Assisted with problem solving for IT and Telecommunications.
- Supervised and delegated tasks to a team of [20] people.
- Proactively participated in meetings and helped create new practices.
- Coached new Agents as for the technical and CS related procedures.